percentmobile.com 2011-11-23

# Privacy Policy - PercentMobile

TigTags Corporation, described herein as (the “Company”) is a provider of analytics technology and services to websites, brands, marketers, and application providers, and considers the protection of your privacy to be of paramount importance. This Privacy Policy was prepared to describe how we use and collect consumer data in providing these services, specifically PercentMobile, described herein as (the “Service”).

## Data Collection and Usage

##### Personal Information (Not collected)

Personal information is data that is personally identifiable like name, address, email address, or phone number, that is not otherwise publicly available. The Service has no place in its system for such visitor information, in direct contrast to some analytics providers. Please refer to their privacy policies. 

The Company never uses, collects or keeps personal information about people who interact with any of the sites using the PercentMobile service.

##### Non-Personal Information

When you are on one of the websites (using TigTags Corporation products and services), the website, using cookies (see below), collects certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, and your operating system. In addition, the sites in the network collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the websites, referring URLs which brought you to those web sites, and click-stream data, none of which will include personal information about you.

##### Cookies

When you visit PercentMobile, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. The Service uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. By using these cookies, we can "remember" what you have done on the Service before and personalize our site for you. These persistent types of cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different, so please look through your browser "Help" file to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up. Please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing some of the functionality and site offerings available via the Service.

##### Automatically Collected Information

When you use the Service or open one of our emails or text messages, we may record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons". This "automatically collected" information may include your Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Service, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit.

##### Information We Collect and How We Use It

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as our blog, [Mobile Analytics, Simplified](http://mobileanalyticssimplified.com/). However, some of our Services will require the provision of certain personal information. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

##### Information you provide

  * When you sign up for a PercentMobile account or other Company services or promotions that requires registration, we sometimes ask you for personal information (such as your e-mail address and an account password). For certain services, such as our premium offerings, we also request credit card or other payment account information which will be maintained by third party merchant(s) or payment processor(s) in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Company services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * Percent Mobile account member e-mail addresses are used to contact account holders regarding service updates, confirmations, opt-in surveys and select partner offers. If you would like to opt-out of these e-mails, please see the Opt-out section within e-mails you receive from us or manage your e-mail subscriptions by signing into PercentMobile by clicking here. You may also contact us using the contact information listed below. If you elect to opt-out of further communications, such opt-out will apply only to marketing messages and not to communications regarding service updates and similar matters.
  * Blog e-mail updates are administered by a 3rd party service provider. E-mail addresses provided to them via the automated form on the blog are used solely for the purpose of sending you blog alerts.
  * If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend that you think percentmobile.com might be of interest to them, we will ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. We have no intention of annoying you or your friends. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database. Please be judicious when providing friends' contact information to our service and do not provide us with such information unless you have your friends' consent to do so.
  * When you contact us via our Contact form, send e-mail or other communication we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Google to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Google may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

##### When TigTags Discloses Information

The Company may disclose both personally identifiable and automatically collected information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to process such information on our behalf, to provide website maintenance and security, to offer certain features on the Service, to assist us in improving the way the Service works and looks, and to create new features. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and we require these parties to use any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Service. 

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, TigTags Corporation does not share personal information about PercentMobile users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user's request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in TigTags Corporation’s interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others. 

We do not share User information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

##### User Profile and Password

You have access to your personal information and you may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting User's profile access. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

##### Children

Consistent with the federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13). Any person who uses the Service represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

##### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

TigTags Corporation may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Service. They automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. 

The Company does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

##### Our Commitment to Data Security

We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. 

If the Company learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Service or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of PercentMobile. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us via email at privacy@percentmobile.com.

##### Special Note to International Users

The PercentMobile Service is primarily hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the PercentMobile Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions, and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

##### In the Event of Merger or Sale

If TigTags Corporation should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information the Company receives from you through the PercentMobile service is an asset of the company and may be transferred.

##### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "effective date" on the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information that you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the PercentMobile Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

##### Contacting TigTags

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@tigtags.com or contact us at: TigTags Corporation c/o Engagelogic, 606 Johnson Ave, Suite 25, Bohemia, New York 11716

_Last updated on: 7 September 2010_
